

PERSONAL DETAILS

Name	Travis Harley
Web	http://TravisHarley.com
Contact	801.759.5762
Email	harley.travis2@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Brigham Young University - Online: Class of 2017 Bachelor of Science in Web Development HTML5 & CSS3 Certified - W3 Schools



EXPERIENCE

RizePoint

SLC, Utah Aug 2016 - Present

Web Manager

Responsible for building, enhancing and maintaining RizePoint's internal and external web properties. Build, test, QA and launch web properties and landing pages to help grow the company. Designed and developed new corporate website in 2017. Our site recieved the Gold Marcom award for Website Redesign. Developed internal framework and documention.

Peak Alarm

SLC, Utah Oct 2015 - July 2016

Frontend Developer

Responsible for building and maintaining corporate websites, manage SEO and online marketing campaigns. Designed new corporate websites. Converted design mock-ups into custom WordPress template using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and PHP.

InkSoft

Tempe, Arizona Feb 2014 - Oct 2015

Project Manager

Managed custom software solutions for Alpha Broder. Effectively communicated with our partners and developers on implementing new features for client's custom software. Manage developer's task list and organize upcoming projects. QA testing on application. UX/UI design.

Jestset Magazine

Scottsdale, Arizona Aug 2013 - Jan 2014

Junior Developer - Internship

Designed and developed the user login system for their corporate website. Designed and built the database using PhpMyAdmin. Maintained website content with HTML5 and CSS3, PHP, JSON and JavaScript. Managed WordPress account and updated content for clients.

Marketecture

Orem, Utah Feb 2011 - May 2013

Design Manager

Project managed custom templates for clients. Managed small team of web designers to design and develop custom websites. Coded websites to function within our company API, using PHP and JavaScript. Trained co-workers on company software, HTML and CSS. QA testing on all designs before client approval.



PROFILE



TravisHarley.com PeakAv.net RenterCafe.com

WhiteJuly.com RizePoint.com EastValleyMaid.com

Awards

HTMI 5 CSS3 / SASS / LESS JavaScript / jQuery / AJAX PHP MySql Bootstrap / Foundation

Gold Marcom Website Redesign

W3 Schools HTML5 Certified

W3 Schools CSS3 Certified

State Skills USA Web Dev



Computer

Adobe Creative Suite Adobe Dreamweaver Adobe Photoshop Adobe XD Adobe Ilustrator



Knowledge

WordPress Custom Themes



Hobbies

Filmmaking Music Video Games **Creative Writing** Photography

I'm Travis Harley and I don't question it. I have been developing websites for over five years. I'm always learning to advance my skill-set on a regular basis. In that learning, I have also learned best practices for web development, custom WordPress templates, frameworks, API development, Search Engine Optimization (SEO), online marketing, QA testing, UI/UX design and much more. More importantly, I am a master at The Legend of Zelda. I find inspiration from The Beatles and comic books. In my spare time, I like to film short videos and weekends are my jam.